Gilianne L. Sanjur

Miami, Florida 33136 305.439.4955 GLSANJUR7@GMAIL.COM

SUMMARY

Dedicated Human Resources Generalist with experience in various aspects of human resources management and C-level administration. This includes staff development, a strong emphasis on recruitment, sourcing, retention, policy development, legal compliance, conflict resolution, compensation, benefit plans, and records management. Strong communication skills, attention to detail and the ability accurately anticipate needs.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SW CORP: 2019 - Present Human Resources

Responsibilities:

- Plan and implement company talent acquisition strategy
- Develop the company's policy for talent benchmarking, talent assessment and interviewing
- Conduct sourcing activities in order to fill open positions
- Perform analysis of organizational development and anticipate future employment needs
- Design and manage recruitment and selection processes (resume screening, screening calls, interviews, etc.)
- Reviews employment applications and background check reports
- Serve as a brand ambassador at various events, like career fairs or on-campus recruiting events
- Counsel the candidate on corporate benefits, salary, and corporate environment
- Build long-term relationships with past and potential candidates
- Manage respective candidate pools to ensure qualified candidates remain engaged in current or future opportunities
- Administer and submit all hiring paperwork for new employees
- Generate monthly updates for the company's leadership about upcoming talent acquisition initiatives
- Create monthly reports on key talent acquisition metrics
- Communicate regularly with the HR department to get a clear view of the company's hiring needs and organizational goals
- Work closely with the marketing department to develop creative ways for addressing talent acquisition challenges
- Proactively seek market intelligence to gain a competitive advantage in attraction, assessment and sourcing methodologies
- Suggest new ideas for improving talent acquisition activities
- Research talent acquisition trends in the staffing industry

Falcon Americas Group: 2010 - 2018

Human Resources Generalist and Executive Assistant

Responsibilities:

- Support current and future business needs through the development, engagement, motivation, and preservation of human capital
- Talent acquisition and recruitment processes

- Conduct employee onboarding and help organize training & development initiatives
- Assist in the development and implementation of human resource policies
- Ensure legal compliance with labor regulations throughout human resource management
- Provide support to employees in various HR-related topics such as leaves, compensation and resolve any issues that may arise
- Oversee and manage a performance appraisal system that drives high performance
- Organize quarterly and annual employee performance reviews
- Maintain employee files and records in electronic and paper form
- Develop and implement HR strategies and initiatives aligned with the overall business strategy
- Bridge management and employee relations by addressing demands, grievances or other issues
- Nurture a positive working environment enhancing job satisfaction by resolving issues promptly, applying for new perks, benefits and organizing team-building activities to boost employee morale.
- Develop a compensation strategy and benefit plans
- Assess training needs to apply and monitor training programs
- Report to management and provide decision support through HR metrics
- Coordinate daily calendars of CEO
- Act as the point of contact between executives and employees/clients
- Create regular reports and update internal databases
- Make travel arrangements and manage phone calls and emails on behalf of CEO
- Facilitate internal communication
- Suggest more efficient ways to run the office and troubleshoot malfunctions

ADDITIONAL PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Painting with a Twist Coral Gables: 2015 - Present

Franchisee

EDUCATION

Albizu University

M.S. in Industrial & Organizational Psychology Present

Albizu University

Bachelor of Business Administration 2014

Miami Senior High School

High School Diploma 2008

LICENSES AND CERTIFICATIONS

Florida Notary Public

REFERENCES

Available upon your request